singles2meet.co.za 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy for Singles2Meet.co.za

Privacy Policy

We at Singles2meet.co.za value every user and want your online experience to be as good as it can possibly be.

We will only use user information collected for identification and contact purposes.

Information collected by us will not be shared with anybody. We will not give out or sell the information you provide us with.

Singles2meet.co.za does not sell or rent its e-mail lists to third parties. It is against our policy to provide any user information to any third party without the users's prior permission.

Singles2meet.co.za does not send unsolicited or "spam" e-mail. We will only send email to communicate new information to you or to inform you of important information regarding your profile at Singles2meet.co.za. All users are given the opportunity to unsubscribe at any time.

Our service can also be discontinued entirely if you don't want to participate anymore. Your information will be removed from our systems completely after you closed your account.

The privacy of our visitors to Singles2Meet.co.za is important to us.

At Singles2Meet.co.za, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Below is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Singles2Meet.co.za, and how we safeguard your information.

Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to your account.

We also use third party advertisements on Singles2Meet.co.za to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Pretoria real estate ads to someone in Pretoria, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all web sites using this advertising by visiting [DoubleClick](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into your dating profile here.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

Email Policy

Singles2Meet.co.za does not send unsolicited email. All accounts on Singles2Meet.co.za must be confirmed by clicking a link inside an email sent to you. We will not send you email if your account is not confirmed. By confirming your account you agree to receive email from us, but keep in mind that the email notifications we send to you can also be turned off.

Once an account is confirmed and activated we will send you notifications by email to inform you when other members of Singles2Meet.co.za has contacted you. You may then log into Singles2meet.co.za to read the messages you have received from other members. We also send other notifications which can be turned off by clicking a link inside the bottom of the particular email notification to disable the notification.

**To turn off notifications manually do the following:**  
1\. Log into your account at singles2meet.co.za  
2\. Click on 'Profile'  
3\. Then click on 'Basic Details'  
4\. You will be presented with options to turn off specific notifications.

We will never make your email address available to any third parties. We do not sell email addresses.

**If you would like to completely end your account at Singles2Meet.co.za then do the following:  
**1\. Click on 'Profile'.  
2\. Click on 'Basic Details'.  
3\. Under 'PROFILE VISIBILITY' choose: 'Delete profile'.  
4\. Click on 'Save Basic Details and Settings'

Once your account is ended we will never again send email to you and your account details is permanently removed from our database.
